[
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_111",
        "question": "A 60-year-old female presents with a non-healing painful ulcer on her right leg for 4 months. <br>- She says she first noticed it after she accidentally bumped into a chair. <br>- She is known for rheumatoid arthritis and hypertension, and has taken methotrexate and bisoprolol for years. <br>- According to the patient, oral antibiotics and wound debridement have only increase the size of the ulcer. <br>- Physical exam reveals a 5x5 cm fibrinous ulcer with violaceous undermined borders on her right shin.",
        "option1": "Venous ulcer",
        "option2": "Traumatic wound",
        "option3": "Pyoderma grangrenosum",
        "option4": "Arterial ulcer",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "53%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_022",
        "question": "A 42-year-old man presents with a four-day history of experiencing headache, malaise, and stabbing right-sided headache. <br>- Two days after his initial symptoms appeared, he developed a rash over the area of pain. <br>- He reports that he went hiking through the Texas hill country prior to becoming ill. <br>- The patient is otherwise in good health and has an unremarkable medical history. <br>- Physical examination reveals unilateral erythematous, thin, raised plaques over the right forehead. <br>- In addition, he has no relevant social or family history.",
        "option1": "Contact dermatitis",
        "option2": "Zosteriform herpes simplex",
        "option3": "Scabies",
        "option4": "Herpes zoster",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "44%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_065",
        "question": "An elderly man presents with asymptomatic hyperpigmented, confluent, brown macules on his upper and lower lips, along with hyperpigmented macules on his hands. <br>- He also has diffuse blue-black bilateral melanonychia with nail dystrophy on his toenails, and his fingernails contain longitudinal melanonychia with hyperpigmentation of the proximal nail beds. <br>- He denies any family history of mucocutaneous pigmentation or gastrointestinal or systemic symptoms. <br>- In the last 5 years, results of a colonoscopy, upper gastrointestinal endoscopy, and blood work have all been within normal limits.",
        "option1": "Bandler syndrome",
        "option2": "Peutz-Jeghers syndrome",
        "option3": "Laugier-Hunziker syndrome",
        "option4": "McCune-Albright syndrome",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "70%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_062",
        "question": "A 26-year-old African American man with no significant past medical history presents with a growth on his left foot that had been increasing in size for 1 year. <br>- He initially thought it was a wart but had concerns when it continued to grow and became painful. <br>- Examination reveals an exophytic, brown, and mildly tender nodule, 3cm in diameter, on his left medial heel and instep. <br>- The overlying skin is crusted and friable. <br>- His nails and hair show no abnormalities. <br>- There is no associated lymphadenopathy. <br>- The remainder of the examination is unremarkable.",
        "option1": "Ulcers",
        "option2": "Dysplastic nevus",
        "option3": "Acral lentiginous melanoma",
        "option4": "Hematomas",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "55%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_055",
        "question": "A 50-year-old woman presents with a 5-day history of progressive, painful rash involving her face, trunk, extremities, nasal tip, and ears, in addition to fever and arthralgia. <br>- She admits to a history of polysubstance use and states that her last use was a week prior to symptom onset. <br>- She denies a history of autoimmune disease or recent travel. <br>- Examination reveals retiform purpura with areas of necrosis and bullae formation. <br>- Urine toxicology screening is positive for cocaine, and laboratory findings include leukopenia and an elevated erythrocyte sedimentation rate (70 mm/h).",
        "option1": "Tinea incognito",
        "option2": "Warfarin-induced skin necrosis",
        "option3": "Disseminated intravascular coagulation",
        "option4": "Levamisole-induced antineutrophil cytoplasmic antibody vasculitis",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "92%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_054",
        "question": "A 43-year-old elementary school teacher presents with a rash that began on his left thigh approximately 4 months earlier; the rash has since spread. <br>- It is mildly itchy but has no associated pain or bleeding. <br>- His past medical history is significant for allergic rhinitis and atopic dermatitis. <br>- Suspecting eczema, he has been applying an over-the-counter hydrocortisone 1% cream as well as a moisturizer, which transiently alleviates the itch. <br>- He has not changed laundry or hygiene products. <br>- On physical examination, there are slightly erythematous, minimally scaly patches scattered over his left hip and buttock.",
        "option1": "Cutaneous lupus",
        "option2": "Eczema",
        "option3": "Tinea incognito",
        "option4": "Levamisole-induced antineutrophil cytoplasmic antibody vasculitis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "80%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_025",
        "question": "An 8-year-old African-American boy presents with a 3-day history of fever, pain, and a rash on his trunk. <br>- On examination, the patient has several fragile, bullous lesions on his trunk, many of which have eroded, exposing erythematous, annular lesions. <br>- The patient is febrile and shaking in the office, and he appears to be in pain. <br>- He has no other relevant social or family history and does not take any medications. <br>- His mother is very concerned about her son.",
        "option1": "Bullous impetigo",
        "option2": "Bullous erythema multiforme",
        "option3": "Autoimmune bullous dermatoses",
        "option4": "Stevens-Johnson syndrome",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "91%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_121",
        "question": "A 6 month old male presents to dermatology clinic for evaluation of skin depressions on the arms and legs present for a few months. <br>- The patient's mother denies any trauma that may have incited the depressions. <br>- Lesions are not painful or itchy to the patient. <br>- Mother denies any recent travel or treatments. <br>-   Past medical history is relevant for full term prenatal course. <br>- At birth, patient was noted to be red across the entire body with thin flaky yellow skin attached to the back and chest which slowly healed. <br>- Recently, patient was also evaluated by orthopaedics and completed a hand x-ray that showed epiphyseal stippling. <br>-   Physical examination is remarkable for multiple follicular based depressions a curvilinear distribution on the hands, legs, and feet on the hands, legs, and feet. <br>-  What is the most likely diagnosis?",
        "option1": "Nicolau-Balus syndrome",
        "option2": "Bazex-Dupre-Christol syndrome",
        "option3": "Rombo syndrome",
        "option4": "Conradi-HÃ¼nermann-Happle syndrome",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "41%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_079",
        "question": "A 42-year-old Hispanic man with no prior medical history presents with a 2-month history of a rash on his face, chest, and arms. <br>- He reports that the rash gets worse after sun exposure and he has associated joint pain. <br>- He has taken over-the-counter nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drugs (NSAIDs) for the joint pain and topical steroids for the rash with no symptomatic relief. <br>- Physical examination reveals erythematous patches over the malar cheeks and dorsal nose sparing the nasolabial fold and erythematous macules on the forearms and chest.",
        "option1": "Acne rosacea",
        "option2": "Seborrheic dermatitis",
        "option3": "Systemic lupus erythematosus",
        "option4": "Dermatitis",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "87%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_057",
        "question": "A 64-year-old woman presents with a 6-month history of a slowly enlarging bump near her left eyebrow. <br>- The patient says it appeared suddenly and became a nuisance, as well as cosmetically unacceptable as it enlarged. <br>- She denies any pain, tenderness, or oozing, and denies any other similar lesions elsewhere. <br>- Her pertinent dermatologic medical and family history are unremarkable. <br>- Physical examination reveals a 6-mm nontender subcutaneous mobile nodule on the left lateral eyebrow. <br>- There is no overlying ulceration or central punctum, and no discharge is noted. <br>- No other suspicious lesions are observed on examination of the scalp and face, aside from mild actinic damage.",
        "option1": "Pilar cyst",
        "option2": "Pilomatricoma",
        "option3": "Squamous cell carcinoma",
        "option4": "Nodulocystic basal cell carcinoma",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "69%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_128",
        "question": "A 30 year old male is admitted to the hospital for a rash that developed on the chest and then spread across the back, face, and legs. <br>- He recently started lamotrigine two weeks ago for seizure prevention. <br>- He denies any other recent medication changes. <br>- He endorses significant pain at the site of the rash and also pain with urination. <br>-   Physical examination reveals diffuse pink erythematous patches of the chest, back with few scattered dusky central patches. <br>- Applying pressure with a finger and moving laterally results in separation of the skin on many areas of the back. <br>- A thin erosion is appreciated on the glans penis.",
        "option1": "Morbilliform eruption",
        "option2": "Acute Generalized Exanthematous Pustulosis",
        "option3": "Drug-induced hypersensitivity syndrome",
        "option4": "Steven Johnsons Syndrome",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "85%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_123",
        "question": "A 45-year-old-man with a past medical history of knee pain and hypertension complains of dark spot on the lower lip that develop whenever he takes certain oral medications. <br>- He states the rash has been ongoing for several years, and usually begins as a pink spot with a darker brown-black center. <br>- He denies any bleeding or ulceration at the site. <br>-  Current medications includes naproxen, multivitamins, and metoprolol. <br>-   Physical examination reveals a well demarcated red-purple patch with a darker red-violaceous center. <br>- The patch is non-painful.",
        "option1": "Morbilliform Drug Eruption",
        "option2": "Fixed Drug Eruption",
        "option3": "Steven Johnson Syndrome",
        "option4": "Erythema migrans",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "45%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_018",
        "question": "A 38-year-old African American woman was referred to dermatology because of spots on her torso and arms. <br>- The lesions were asymptomatic, but their development, cause, and cosmesis were of concern. <br>- No benefit was seen with the use of OTC remedies such as hydroxycortisone 1% cream or vitamin E oil. <br>- Her medical history was significant for systemic lupus erythematosus, well controlled on hydroxychloroquine. <br>- Physical examination revealed numerous, well-circumscribed, 0.5- to 2-cm, hypopigmented, round-to-oval macules of wrinkled skin on her anterior chest wall, back, abdomen, and bilateral upper arms. <br>- Invagination of the lesions was noted with palpation. <br>- A punch biopsy was performed.",
        "option1": "Anetoderma associated with SLE",
        "option2": "Post-inflammatory elastolysis",
        "option3": "Cutis laxa",
        "option4": "Mid-dermal elastolysis",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "48%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_067",
        "question": "A 68-year-old white man presents with 4 weeks of progressively worsening thickening of the skin and plaques on the bilateral nipple and areola. <br>- He has no personal or family history of warts or epidermal nevi and has not had hormonal therapy. <br>- On examination, he has hyperpigmented, verrucous plaques bilaterally, with no associated erythema or lymphadenopathy. <br>- Skin biopsy shows hyperkeratosis with papillomatosis. <br>- Corticosteroid treatment failed, but there was some minor improvement with calcipotriol after several weeks of use.",
        "option1": "Chronic eczema",
        "option2": "Nipple hyperkeratosis",
        "option3": "Darier disease",
        "option4": "Acanthosis nigricans",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "71%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_001",
        "question": "A 51-year-old white man presents to the clinic with a 2-year history of a painful, recurrent rash on his fingers. <br>- He initially noticed redness, irritation, and pustules around his nails that he thought were caused by an infection. <br>- However, the rash progressed to affect the nail bed, eventually destroying his nails. <br>- On examination, well-demarcated, scaly plaques with associated pustules and nail atrophy are present on the right second and third distal digits. <br>- He is otherwise healthy.",
        "option1": "Herpetic whitlow",
        "option2": "Acrodermatitis continua of Hallopeau",
        "option3": "Acute contact dermatitis",
        "option4": "Paronychia",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "46%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    }
]